hotrussianbrides.com 2005-04-29

# Our Privacy Policy

The following privacy policy (the “Privacy Statement”) is posted by Romantic Tours, Inc. as the owner and operator of this web site under the trademark [**HotRussianBrides.com**](http://www.hotrussianbrides.com/). Romantic Tours, Inc. has a strong commitment to providing excellent service to its customers, while respecting their concerns about privacy and security. This statement contains general and technical details about the steps we take to protect you and your information. 

1\. Information Collection: 

Romantic Tours, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on [**HotRussianBrides.com**](http://www.hotrussianbrides.com/). Romantic Tours, Inc. collects information at different points as you access the web site. 

During membership registration, a user must first complete the Profile and Preferences pages and provide an email address. This information will never be sold or otherwise made available to third parties. We will only disclose your personal information if required by law. Occasionally, we may send information to your personal email account concerning important changes or updates to our web site. 

When a user utilizes anyone of our pay services, the user must provide personal contact and financial information such as credit card number, expiration date, and user's mailing address. This information is used for billing purposes only, and will never be divulged to any third parties, unless required by law.   
  
2\. Information Use: 

[**HotRussianBrides.com**](http://www.hotrussianbrides.com/) may only be used for lawful purposes by individuals with genuine intentions of starting a meaningful relationship. 

**Profile  **  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that detail their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the user's personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our site, and access relevant information. Email address lists are not sold to any third party. 

**Cookies  **  
There are two types of cookies, "Persistent" and "Session ID". A persistent cookie is a very small text file placed on your hard drive by a web server. It is essentially your identification card, and cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. It is uniquely yours and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. The persistent cookies are set to expire in 60 days and may change at any time without prior notice. 

Session ID's cookies are used to provide you with correct formatting and to move data between pages. Once the users close the browser, the cookie(s) simply terminates. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

Setting a session ID cookie enables us to present you with correct formatting and users will not have to login more than once. If the users choose to reject the cookie(s), they may still browse our web site, although the database functions and formatting (display) might not function correctly. Persistent cookies are used to recognize repeat visitors.   
**  
Log Files  **  
Like most standard web site servers, we use log files. These log files include information such as Internet protocol (IP) addresses, Internet browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and the number of clicks, to analyze trends, administer the web site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

**Communication from the Web Site  **  
Members will receive a notification message at their personal email address when new messages appear in their [**HotRussianBrides.com**](http://www.hotrussianbrides.com/) mailbox. They can customize this convenience to get a notification once a day, once a week, for every new email they receive, or not at all. To tailor this service, members need only click on “Web Site Preferences” located in the right-hand column of their Account page. On occasion, we may send members promotional messages or announcements that are strictly service related. Members may not opt out of these communications.  

**Sharing  **  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web site. 

**Links  **  
This web site contains links to other web sites. Please be aware that Romantic Tours, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other web sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.   
  
3\. Security:

This web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and offline. When our registration/order process asks users to provide sensitive information (i.e., credit card number) that information is encrypted and protected with encryption software – VeriSign®. 

While we use VeriSign® encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information offline. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job function or task (for example, our accounting department or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment. 

If users have any questions about the security of our web site, an email should be directed to [info@HotRussianBrides.com](mailto:info@HotRussianBrides.com). 

4\. Correcting / Updating / Deleting / Deactivating Personal Information: 

If a user's personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires our services, we provide a way for you to correct, update, delete and/or deactivate this information online. In the event you experience difficulty, an email should be directed to [info@HotRussianBrides.com](mailto:info@HotRussianBrides.com). 

5\. Notification of Changes:

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes to this Privacy Statement either on the homepage, and/or any other conspicuous place within the web site that we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we would or would not disclose it. 

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify users both via email and by posting a notice on our web site for 30 days. In the event that a user has opted out of all communication with the web site, or deleted/deactivated the account prior to the change, there will be no communication, nor will their information be used in this new manner. 

6\. Contact Information: 

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:   
**Email:** [info@HotRussianBrides.com](mailto:info@HotRussianBrides.com)   
**Address:** 1415 Pinehurst Rd., Suite K   
Dunedin, FL 34698
